Finding Aid for Vogel’s & Wurster’s records, 1883-1959
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Vogel’s & Wurster’s records 1883-1959
Vogel’s & Wurster’s (Chelsea, Mich.)
9 oversize volumes
2011135 BB Outsize
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were the gift of Jack Winans (donor no. 10652 ) and came to the library in October 2011.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
Vogel's & Wurster's was a Chelsea, Michigan mercantile establishment. The firm was known as H.S. Holmes Mercantile Company from the 1880s to about 1916. The firm was then reorganized as Vogel's & Wurster's. Dallas H. Wurster and Edward Vogel had previously served as secretary and treasurer of the Holmes firm. Sometime after World War II, the store was renamed Vogel's & Foster's.
The Vogel & Wurster business records consists of ledgers, financial journals, and other business records primarily in the period when the firm was known as H.S. Holmes Mercantile Company from the 1880s to about 1916.
Subjects:
H.S. Holmes Mercantile Company (Chelsea, Mich.); Vogel's & Wurster's (Chelsea, Mich.); Clothing trade--Michigan--Chelsea.; Chelsea (Mich.)--Commerce.
- Vogel & Wurster business records
  - Ledger, 1933-1959 (Volume 1)
  - Journal, 1944-1952 (Volume 2)
  - Daybook, 1947-1951 (Volume 3)
  - H.S. Holmes cashbook, 1913-1914 (Volume 4)
  - H.S. Holmes ledger, 1887-1888 (Volume 5)
  - H.S. Holmes salesbook, 1909-1912 (Volume 6)
  - H.S. Holmes index (Volume 7)
  - H.S. Holmes index (Volume 8)
  - H.S. Holmes stockbook, 1883-1904 (Volume 9)